Filler paper [music]
GPA up to so at Target. These are my F.
[music]
It's time.
Not that time. It's back to school time.
Back to school has officially defrosted.
It's been defrosted. I'm just now
getting school supplies. Of course, I
have to wait till the last minute. Open
house for school is tomorrow. I got my
schedule today. I'm a little bit gagged
by my schedule. Some of the classes I
didn't even pick and they just threw me
in them. I never knew that I'd be taking
an engineering class in my entire life,
but here I am. And what's the school
supplies do you even get for that? So,
this is going to be an interesting
adventure. We have a couple stores that
we're going to visit and hopefully
everything isn't sold out cuz it
probably will be.
[music]
Should I hard launch my belly button
piercing to the vlog?
Do you guys like it? I like it. [music]
It didn't even hurt you guys. I was so
scared of it and everyone was saying,
"Oh my god, 10,000 out [music] of 10." I
got to the piercing shop. There was so
much drama because I went to one
piercing shop and they said I didn't
have the right anatomy and I was like,
"I know you're lying [music] because
I've seen so many people get it with my
anatomy." So, I went to another shop and
they were like, "That person was wrong.
You do have the right anatomy." I'm
like, "Yes, wait, now I have to do
actual piercing." It was the easiest
piercing ever. And [music]
scientifically, it's supposed to be the
second least most painful least painful.
And it literally was a 2 out of [music]
10. It didn't hurt really at all. I was
just psyched for no reason. And now I
have a beautiful diamonds in my belly
button or titanium. [music] Same thing.
[music]
Here we are.
Where did that go? Oh,
>> so if I have eight classes, let's think
of the classes I have. AP modern, I'm
definitely going to need a binder for
that one. Geometry. I feel like I'm
going to need that, too. For science,
English,
I can use notebooks, but I didn't even
use my freaking notebook for English
last year. I just used my folder. Maybe
I'll get like three notebooks just to
[music] be safe. Oh, wait. They have
turquoise. Maybe I can get one pink, one
turquoise, and another one pink. The
turquoise ones can be science, but I
can't reach it. Purple,
>> pink. Think about it. Last year, I had a
bunch of paper. I think I'll definitely
be able to fit a folder if I keep it
organized and I empty out the work that
I finish and like re like take out the
papers I don't need anymore. Then this
[music] will definitely fit everything.
I think I'm going to get two of those.
Oh yeah, maybe I can get like stickers.
I have so many stickers in like my
decorate.
I think I want to get these. These are
cute. Wait, where do I want [music] to
get these? You know, I like these
specific pen I must use. It's a Pilot
G10. Do you think when it comes to
school supplies, I'm going to need like
colored pencils? Do you think we're
going to be getting artsy or
highlighters? [music] I want cute ones.
Maybe Target will have those.
>> Okay.
>> Get this one. Or do you think I should
get
this one, which is like Oh, they were
just they were just in between each
other. I thought they were different.
Wait, so I get these two? Do y'all think
[music] these are cute or should I just
get white to be basic?
[snorts] Guys, look how cute. I like
pastel.
I I like I like them all.
I like the colors, too. It's a colorful
year.
[music]
I always look at staples cuz these
colors are not they're not matching the
pastel. They're too
bright. [laughter]
Oh,
[music]
Walmart is done, Zel, you guys. So, it's
time to go into
Target. I don't know why I'm back
shopping at Target. I just am. They have
good school supplies. They have good
everything. tried to boycott it forever.
And I still believe in why I boycotted
it. I only come here for essentials. I
don't go here just for fun. But yeah,
guys, let's let's enter Target. Watch me
pull up in this. Guys, I'm looking for
[music] a Spider-Man shirt because I
need [clears throat] like a Spider-Man
baby because I'm going to see Brand New
[music] Day today with my like friends.
And I want to be really cute and have a
cute little Spider-Man
tank top though.
>> 5T 3. 5T. Y'all [music] think 5T is
going to fit me? I think 5T could
probably fit me. Guys, this will for
sure fit.
I think I could even go smaller. I need
it to be tight, though. That still looks
like pretty big.
I think it'll fit. I swear this is a
good size. This is a really good size. I
think this is my um my shirt.
>> You know Bad Buddy in the new [music]
Spider-Man?
>> Yeah, I do. Boo.
See, I'm going be like, guys, I think
it's cute.
>> Okay,
>> it's just the head hole is a little
small, but it'll work.
[music]
>> I think Love Check Fancy is a little bit
too overboard for me. I think I need a
little bit more to Okay, so this is like
locker stuff. I'm not really a fan of
like the color patterns you got going
on. Have a cute backpack, girl. But I
have my school bag. I'm happy. So, what
do we need here? We need folders and I
need pens. Let me know if you see
[music] pilot. Oh, I see pilot. These
other colors are just too vibrant. I
can't. So, I think it will match like
the color scheme more if I get. Okay, so
I just want to get a folder for every
class. Plan is guys, we got some
folders, like [music] seven of them. I
got my little shirt and I'm just trying
to get the baseline stuff. We're about
to go to the front and get my favorite
pens so [music] that I can have all that
kind of stuff. But I do have a lot of
stuff from last year that I also kept
for the school year because I tried to
like keep them with me and not like give
my pencils [music] out to everybody
because in eighth grade I did that and I
literally ended the year with not a
single pencil and having to borrow
everyone else's pencils. [music] And
also tomorrow the open house they're
going to let us know like what supplies
we're going to need so we can come back
and get more stuff. [music]
>> Bolt 1 mm.
>> Well, now that we got a planner, [music]
do we really need to go to stables? That
is cute. But I like the kind of color
scheme I have going on. [music]
[music]
I'm a little bit sick under the weather.
My throat was tatling at the beginning
of this video and now I'm actually sick
and I'm coughing and sneezing and not
being able to be breathing. Ooh, think
that kind of rhymed. Bars. But yeah, you
guys, I need to give you this back to
school haul of all of my supplies. Mind
you, I still have stuff from last year
that I have like index cards, sticky
notes, also pencils, and other stuff.
So, if you're wondering, Kennedy, why
are you missing half of your school
supplies? It's because I have them from
last year. I just wanted to kind of get
the the fundamentals. Since I filmed the
beginning of this video, we actually had
our back to school open house, so I was
able to go visit all my teachers, see my
school supply list, and I took pictures
of all of them, and it seems like I'm
pretty secured when it comes to classes.
I'm happy with the amount of things that
I got. It's kind of perfect, and it fits
everything, and it's going to be great.
It's going to be cute. It's going to be
light and cute. But yeah, let's get into
this haul. My bag's laid out here on the
floor. It's not too much, but it's also
not a small amount. Yeah, let's get into
it. I got this really cute three- ring
binder. Simple. It's purple. I got them
in multiple colors. This year, I will
admit, is a very colorful school supply
season, and I'm happy about it. It's got
like a pastel, white, beiges, nudes, all
that kind of theme, light colors. I like
it, but honestly, very pastely. It'll
fit all my stuff. I just need to like
think of what binder is going to be for
what subject. So, I need to organize
that. Maybe I'll put stickers and
labels.
Wait, I kind of like back to school. I'm
kind of excited. Getting into notebooks.
I have three notebooks that I got. And I
think it'll be cool because I got kind
of like similar colors to the binders.
So, maybe like this purple one can be
for the same subject as the purple
binder. I don't know. I'll kind of
figure that out. But I got three
notebooks and they're all in cute
colors. I got this purple one. I got
this cyan/turquoisey
teal one. Love this color. This is
actually my year of birth color, which I
think is really cool. It's like teal.
And then I got, of course, a classic
pink notebook because I love pink and
pink is my favorite color. And I feel
like having cute school supplies
motivates me to want to do cute school
stuff [music] and get good grades. I
honestly think if I get anything under a
95, I failed. Maybe just a mental thing,
but I think it's a good thing. Oh, my
hair's actually like flat in the back.
Who was going to tell me? Why don't you
guys tell me? Okay, moving on. I got
these really cute mechanical pencils and
they look very pastely rainbow. I like
them a lot. They have the erasers that
go with them. It's kind of like a DIY
moment. Why they got the erasers
separated from the pencils? Okay,
Papermate, build your own pencil, I
guess.
[cough]
Moving on. This is a big bag. This one's
got a lot. Okay. Yes, I got this binder
right here. It's white. Cute. three-
ring binder. I need to figure out what
subject this is going to be for. I only
got two binders, which is completely
okay because I think I only need [music]
two binders.
Everything else, I think I can use a
folder in a notebook or just some loose
leaf, which I think is going to be good.
Speaking of loose leaf, I got two packs
of loose leaf filler paper. I'm going to
put them inside of my binders and then
I'm going to put the folder inside of
the binder. So then it's kind of like a
paper and folder moment, which we love.
I did that last year and it honestly was
so convenient. I did it for my math work
and I did it for my history work.
Especially for my history work, it was
really convenient because I could take
all of my notes on the loose leaf and
then I could put all of the assignments
into the folder and it was really really
convenient for me. And that class
honestly became one of my favorite
classes because I felt so like
organized. I'm not feeling very
organized right now though because I'm
sick. Okay, this isn't necessarily for
school. This is a charging cable because
funny story I think I like sat on my
computer charger and that computer
charger is the same charger I used to
charge my iPad and my phone and my
computer. So I think I sat on it and it
broke a little bit and then it was just
open wiring. I continued to use it and
then my dad just completely confiscated
it for me because he was like Kennedy
you cannot use this anymore. You're
going to start a fire. So now I have no
charger and I've just been hopping
around the house trying to find a
charger to use on all of my devices. So
no more do we have to do this. I got
this Heyday charging cable and it's pink
and it's a 10 ft cord. Moving on to back
to like actual school supply. Sorry, I
got a little distracted. Look at these
highlighters, you guys. They're super
cute. I feel like they're really dainty.
They're all in the pasty colors to match
like my folders and my binders and all
that kind of stuff. I really like it.
These are going to be nice to go in my
little pencil case if I need to
highlight something in AP SEM and AP
Modern World History, which are the
classes that I'm taking this year. I
don't know why I decided to take AP SEM.
Apparently, it's very, very hard. And
for these AP exams, I've also heard
they're very hard. So, I'm going to be
taking a lot of notes. And apparently,
they don't guide you with the notes. You
just have to take notes like a college
class. So, I'm a little bit scared. This
is my first AP class, but it's going to
be all good. I'm trying to get this on
my, you know, college record. It's going
to be great. Got to keep that GPA up,
too. Oh, and then I also got a block for
my charger. A pink block. I like it. And
then lastly, in this bag, I got these
sticky notes. And you guessed it,
they're pink, yellow, and teal because
they match my colors and I think they're
really cute. [music] Okay, we have one
more bag. Let's get her out. We have
seven folders here because I think I'm
going to need a folder for every glass,
which is smart. So, we have the two
pocket folders right here, and I just
got seven of them. They're all white.
I'm going to try to like put stickers or
decorate them so I can like tell them
apart, but yeah, I think they'll come in
handy for sure. And then I got [snorts]
this really cute 26 27 agenda slash like
planner which I can put all of my tests
and goals and daily things that I have
to do in here. And it's really really
good for staying organized and being on
top of my work because I feel like a
without a planner I would not be on top
of my work andor organized. And then
moving on to the last item we have of
the school supply. My favorite pens.
These are my favorite pens in the entire
universe. Juicy pen. These are the Pilot
G2 pens in uh 1 mm black ink. Super
smooth, quick drying, refillable, and
bold. Oh my gosh, they work so well.
Writing with them, I feel so like when I
write with them, it's such an amazing
sensation. [music] It's beautiful. It's
smooth. It's super juicy and creamy.
Literally love it. These are the number
one longest writing versus top gel brand
premium gel [music] roller. And they
have a comfort grip and they last
forever. I got five of these pens and
they're going straight into the pencil
case. So, it may not be super aesthetic
like these other things, but they're so
functional that I'm ignoring how
unesthetic they are. Like I said in the
beginning, I have so many other school
supplies from last year that I'm going
to be using. So, don't be concerned, you
guys. I have everything I need, I'm
pretty sure. But, I think I'm going to
end this video right here. If you stayed
all the way to the end of the video,
ooh, comment like any school supplies
emojis, like a pencil, a backpack, a
notebook, [music] anything. Anyways,
thank you guys so much for watching this
video. Make sure you like and subscribe.
New videos coming out every single week.
Stay [music] tuned for more fun back to
school content and I'll see you guys in
my next one. Bye-bye.